hikaribox.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Notice - www.LightInTheBox.com

LightInTheBox.com respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protect your privacy, we provide the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   

## LightInTheBox's Privacy Policy

Thank you for accessing the website, mobile applications, devices and other software (collectively, the "Site") of LightInTheBox.com (all references to “us” and “our" refer to LightInTheBox.com). We respect your privacy and want you to know about the Privacy Policy policies we have in place to protect your personal information. This Private Policy also applies through our services and products via mobile devices, either through mobile applications or mobile-optimized websites.

This Privacy Policy explains:  
How we collect, use, and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information.  
The steps we’ve taken to secure your personal information.  
Your options regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information.

This Privacy NoticePolicy applies only to this website and does not necessarily apply to personal information we collect from you offline. Please see the section on Offline Collection, Use & Disclosure of Information details.Site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website other than LightInTheBox.comthis Site, to which this Site links or that links to this Site.

**By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Notice.**                       
How does LightInTheBox.com collect information about me?  
How does LightInTheBox.com use my personal information?   
How are cookies and other technologies used to collect information?  
Does LightInTheBox.com ever give out my personal information?  
How does LightInTheBox.com secure information collected about me?  
What choices do I have about LightInTheBox.com’s collection of my information?   
Visitors from the European Union?  
Are children allowed to use LightInTheBox.com?  
Where can I find updates to this policy? 

#### How does LightInTheBox.com collect information about me?

We collect information from Site users in several different ways, with the goal of providing an efficient, meaningful, and customized shopping experience. For example, we can use your personal information to: 

   * Register you with our Site and provide you with our services  
   * Record and quickly bring up information you’ve given previously  
   * Help you quickly find information, products, and services  
   * Diagnose and improve Site content to provide you with customer service  
   * provide you with our new information, products, and services

**Registration and Ordering:** In order to use certain parts of this Site or order products, all customers must fill out an online registration form with personal information, including but not limited to, your name, gender, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, we may ask for your country of residence and/or your organization's country of operation, so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. This information is used for billing, order processing and internal marketing as well as to communicate with you about your order and our Site.

**Email Addresses:** Several locations on the Site allow you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: registering for free promotional notices, requesting notification when new brands or product styles arrive, or signing up for our email newsletter. In addition, any participation in promotional contests organized by LightInTheBox.com is completely voluntary and requires disclosure of contact information needed to notify winners and award prizes. We may post the names and cities of contest winners on our Site. 

**Phone Number:** Several locations on the Site allow you to enter your phone number for purposes including but not limited to: SMS verification, registering for free promotional notices, requesting notification when new brands or product styles arrive, or signing up for our SMS newsletter.

**Log Files:** Like most websites, the Site server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access this Site. We may also log your Internet protocol (IP) address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.) 

**Product Reviews:** We ask for an email address and location along with the submission of all product reviews. Your email address will be kept private, but your location will be visible to other users. All other personal information that you choose to submit as part of the review will be available to other visitors to the Site.

#### How does LightInTheBox.com use my personal information?

**Internal Use:** We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may use your personal information internally to collect general information about visitors to this Site, improve Site content and layout, improve our outreach, and market our services and products.

**Communication with You:** We will use your personal information to communicate with you about your orders and our Site. All customers must provide an email address to allow communication with LightInTheBox.com regarding orders placed. We may send you a confirmation email or a SMS verification after you register with us as well as service-related announcements as necessary (for example, temporary suspension of service for maintenance.) You may also submit your email address or phone number to request notification when we receive a new brand, product style or product, or to sign up for our email newsletter, SMS newsletter and special offers. You can unsubscribe or opt out of future emails at any time (see the section of “What choices doe I have about LightInTheBox.com’s collection of my information?” below for more details). 

#### How are cookies and other technologies used to collect information?

Cookies are small pieces of information that your Internet browser stores as text files on your computer's hard drive. Most browsers accept cookies by default, but setting your browser to reject cookies or remove them from your hard drive will prevent you from using parts of this Site. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add products to your shopping cart, proceed to checkout or use any of our services that require you to sign in. The Site uses cookies to:  
   * speed up navigation   
   * track site usage  
   * recognize users and user access privileges and preference   
   * enable and track selection and purchase products on this Site, and record your browsing activity and purchases  
   * conduct research and diagnostics to improve our content, products and services  
   * Improve Site security

On this Site and some unaffiliated sites, we display interest-based advertising using information you make available to us when you interact with our Site, content or services. Interest-based ads, also sometimes referred to as personalized or targeted ads, are displayed to your based on information from activities such as purchasing on the Site, visiting sites that contain our content or ads, interacting with our tools or using our payment services. 

Like other online ad networks, we use cookies, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies, which enable us to learn about what ads you see, what ads you click, and other actions you take on our Sites and other sites. This allows us to provide you with more useful and relevant ads. 

We do not associate your interaction with unaffiliated sites with your identity in providing you with interest-based ads. 

We do not provide any personal information to advertisers or to third party sites that display our interest-based ads. However, advertisers and other third-parties (including the ad networks, ad-serving companies, and other service providers they may use) may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized ad or content are part of the group that the ad or content is directed towards (for example, users in a particular geographical area or users who bought or browsed for classical music). Also, some third-parties may provide us information about you (such as demographic information or sites where you have been shown ads) from offline and online sources that we may use to provide you more relevant and useful advertising. 

Third party advertisers or advertising companies working on their behalf sometimes use technology to serve the advertisements that appear on our Site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that advertisers and third party sites may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third party websites are not covered by our Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

**How to block cookies on your browser?Take Chorme as an example.  
[https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform=Desktop](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform=Desktop)**

Does LightInTheBox.com ever give out my personal information?

We sell merchandise, not information **— We do not sell, rent, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information to anyone, except in the following specific situations:**

     **Third-party service providers:** Like most online retailers, we sometimes use third-party service providers to perform specific functions on our behalf. Any information disclosed to them is solely to help in their provision of service. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, email and phone number to partners such as DHL and UPS in order to guarantee delivery of your orders, and we may use relevant customer information in order to monitor the quality of the third party’s service. Similarly, we must provide your credit card number to financial services organizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order to process payments. We protect all submissions of your credit card number for authorization with state-of-the-art data encryption. (More on this below in the “How does LightInTheBox.com secure information collected about me?” section.)

**Legal requirement to disclose information:** We may be required to disclose information if subpoenaed, served with a court order or requested by law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, or if we are otherwise required by law to disclose such information. We will also release personal information when necessary to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud, or to prevent fraud by users who attempt fraud or other illegal activity on our Site.

**Merger and/or sale of assets:** We do not normally sell, trade or rent personal information   
to other companies in the course of our business. However, it is possible that we might acquire, merge with or be acquired by another company, or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets, in which case your personal information could be disclosed to another company, subject to the Privacy Notice in effect.

**Non-personally identifiable information:** We may share information that does not identify you or any user, such as the number of daily visitors to a particular page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date, with third parties such as advertising partners. 

#### How does LightInTheBox.com secure information collected about me?

This Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as:   
     * Safeguarding all financial transactions done through this Site with Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") encryption   
     * Granting only employees who are providing a specific service access to your personal information   
     * Working only with third-party service providers who we believe adequately secure all computer hardware.   
**While our business is designed with safeguarding your personal information in mind, please remember that 100% security does not presently exist anywhere, online or offline.**

#### What choices do I have regarding LightInTheBox.com’s collection of my information?

You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of certain features on the Site. 

You can choose to:   
     * Correct or update your personal information   
     * Stop receiving mail to your email address    
     * Stop receiving SMS messages to your phones   
     * Disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account   
     * Block cookies on your computer to stop using featured service on the Site   
**To correct or update your personal information** , log in to My Accounts and submit a request through the online Customer Service.   
**To unsubscribe from emails** you receive from LightInTheBox.com, follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email and select the option appropriate for you. Alternatively, you may log into MY Accounts and select the option appropriate to you.   
**To unsubscribe SMS messages** you receive from LightInTheBox.com, log in to My Accounts and select the option appropriate for you.  
**To block the cookies on your computer** the Help feature on most browsers and devices will tell you how to prevent your browser or device from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some essential service on the Site, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your shopping cart or proceed to checkout, or use any of our services that require you to sign in. 

If you are a visitor from the European Union, please refer to "Visitors from the European Union?" as follows for more information

#### Visitors from the European Union?

This section of the Privacy Policy applies only if you use our Site or services covered by this Privacy Policy from a country that is a Member State of the European Union, and supplements the information in this Privacy Policy.

Subject to limitations in applicable law, you are entitled to object to or request the restriction of processing of your personal information, and to request access to, portability, rectification and erasure of your own personal information.  Where the use of your information is based on consent, you can withdraw this consent at any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

**Requests should be submitted by contacting us through our Data Protection Officer at dataprotectionofficer@lightinthebox.com.**

#### Are children allowed to use LightInTheBox.com?

We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. Elsewhere on this Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or are using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian.  
If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you when using the Site.

#### Where can I find updates to this policy?

To keep you informed of what information we collect, use, and disclose, we will post any changes or updates to this Privacy Notice on this Site and encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time. Please contact us with any questions about the Privacy Notice.
